American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
- Series III. Committees, 1906-2005; 1946-1990 bulk; 36 boxes (53.5 linear feet)
  - Subseries III.A. Membership Committee, 1906-1991; 1959-1990 bulk; 618 folders
    - Members: Honorary, 1963-65 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Members: Honorary, 1966-71 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Members: Honorary, 1972-74 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Members: Honorary, 1975-76, 1988-90 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Members: Honorary, Certificates, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Members: Retired, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Members: Retired, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Members: Retired, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Members: Retired, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Members: Retired, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Members: Retired, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Members: Retired, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Members: Retired, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Members: Retired, 1988-90a (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Members: Retired, 1988-90b (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Rating Sheets, 1954, 1958-62, 1964, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Rating Sheets, 1969-72 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Rating Sheets, 1973-77, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Rating Sheets, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Rating Sheets, 1989a (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Rating Sheets, 1989b (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Rating Sheets, 1990a (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Rating Sheets, 1990b (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Reports to Members, 1962-68 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Reports to Members, 1969-76 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Members: Deceased, A (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Members: Deceased, Ba-Bi (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Members: Deceased, Bl-Bu (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Members: Deceased, C (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Members: Deceased, D (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Members: Deceased, E (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Members: Deceased, F (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Members: Deceased, Ga-Gl (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Members: Deceased, Go-Gy (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Members: Deceased, Ha-He (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Members: Deceased, Hi-Hu (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Members: Deceased, I-J (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Members: Deceased, Ka-Ki (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Members: Deceased, Kl-Ky (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Members: Deceased, La-Le (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Members: Deceased, Li-Ly (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Members: Deceased, Ma (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Members: Deceased, Mc-Me (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Members: Deceased, Mi (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Members: Deceased, Mo-My (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Members: Deceased, N (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Members: Deceased, O (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Members: Deceased, P (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Members: Deceased, R (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Members: Deceased, Sa-Sc (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Members: Deceased, Se-Si (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Members: Deceased, Sk-So (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Members: Deceased, Sp-St (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Members: Deceased, Su-Sz (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Members: Deceased, T (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Members: Deceased, U-V (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Members: Deceased, Wa-We (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Members: Deceased, Wh-Wi (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Members: Deceased, Wo-Wy (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Members: Deceased, Y-Z (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Members: Dropped, A (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Members: Dropped, Ba-Be (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Members: Dropped, Bl-Bu (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Members: Dropped, Ca-Ch (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Members: Dropped, Ci-Cr (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Members: Dropped, D (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Members: Dropped, F (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Members: Dropped, G (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Members: Dropped, Ha-He (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Members: Dropped, Hi-Hy (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Members: Dropped, I-J (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Members: Dropped, Ka-Ke (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Members: Dropped, Kh- Ky (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Members: Dropped, L (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Members: Dropped, Ma-Mc (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Members: Dropped, Me-My (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Members: Dropped, N-O (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Members: Dropped, P-Q (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Members: Dropped, Ra-Ri (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Members: Dropped, Ro (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Members: Dropped, Sa-Si (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Members: Dropped, Sl-Sz (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Members: Dropped, T-V (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Members: Dropped, W-Z (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Members: Emeritus, A (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Members: Emeritus, B (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Members: Emeritus, C (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Members: Emeritus, D (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Members: Emeritus, E-Fi (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Members: Emeritus, Fi-Fu (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Members: Emeritus, G (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Members: Emeritus, H (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Members: Emeritus, I-J (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Members: Emeritus, K (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Members: Emeritus, L (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Members: Emeritus, Ma-Mc (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Members: Emeritus, Me-Mu (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Members: Emeritus, N-O (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Members: Emeritus, P-Q (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Members: Emeritus, R (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Members: Emeritus, Sa-Sc (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Members: Emeritus, Se-Sw (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Members: Emeritus, T-Wa (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Members: Emeritus, We-Z (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Members: Honorary, A-K (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Members: Honorary, L-Z (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Members: Resigned, A-F (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Members: Resigned, G-L (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Members: Resigned, M-R (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Members: Resigned, S-Z (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Members: Statistics 1946-1949 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Members: Statistics 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Members: Statistics 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Members: Statistics 1970-1979 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Members: Statistics 1980-1985 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Members: Statistics 1986-1991 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Member Files, Abbott-Acton (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Member Files, Abbott-Acton (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Member Files, Agabian-Aktipis (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Aladjem-Alivisatos (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Allen-Altman (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Altschuld-Amy (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, An-Anderson (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Andrade-Anwar (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Apirion-Aprille (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Arai-Arthur (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Asai-Attie (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Auer-Awasthi (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Ax-Azhar (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Babbitt-Bahl (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Baich-Balazs (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Balch-Baltimore (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Baly-Barbehenn (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Barber-Baron, Jeffrey (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Baron, Louis-Bass (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Bassett-Bauer (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Bauerle-Bazan (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Beach-Bedrosian (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Beeler-Bellino (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Bellion-Bennick (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Bennun-Berger, Edward (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Berger, Nathan-Bernstein (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Bertics-Bezkorovainy (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Bhagwat-Bhushan (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Biaglow-Birnbaum, Edward (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Birnbaum, Morris-Bjercke (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Bjornsson-Blake, Cheryl (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Blake, Richard-Blusztajn (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Bobbitt-Bonaventura (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Bond-Bose (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Bosron-Bower (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Bowers-Boyle (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Braatz-Branca (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Brand-Braymer (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Brechev-Brewer (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Bridger-Broekman (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Brooker-Brown, James (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Brown, Jay-Broze (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Bruening-Brysk (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Bublitz-Bunn (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Burger-Burness (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Burnette-Butler, Emma (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Butler, Larry-Byvoet (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Cabib-Canady (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Candido-Carafoli (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Carbon-Carroll (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Carson-Casnellie (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Caspers-Caulfield (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Cecchini-Cerutti (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Cha-Chan, Peter (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Chan, Samuel-Chang, Hai (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Chang, Kwen-Jen-Chasteen (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Chatterjee-Chazotte (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Cheesbrough-Chen (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Cheng-Chibber (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Chichester-Chlebowski (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Cho-Christopher (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Chu-Chytil (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Ciaranello-Civen (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Clagett-Clark (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Clarke-Clouet (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Cobb-Coffino (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Cohen-Cohen (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Colas-Collins, James (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Collins, Jimmy-Conway (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Cook-Copeland (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Corbin-Costilow (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Cote-Cozzarelli (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Crabb-Cronlund (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Cross-Cunningham (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Cuppoletti-Czerwinski (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Dabbous-Dang (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Dangott-Das, Dipak (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Das, Manjusri-Davio (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Davis-Dayton (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, De-De Haen (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Deibel-Denning (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Dennis-Deutscher (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Dev-Dickson, Leon (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Dickson, Robert-DiMuzio (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Ding-Doebber (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Doeg-Dougherty (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Doughty-Dreyer (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Dreyfus-Dugaiczyk (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Duhamel-Durham (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Dus-Dyson (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Eades-Eckert (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Edelman-Edwards (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Eftink-Eisinger (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Elbein-Elzinga (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Emerich-English (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Englund-Esko (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Esmon-Eyzaguirre (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Fagan-Fanning (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Fanslow-Fayerman (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Feagin-Fenselau (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Fenton-Fietzek (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Fife-Fisher, James (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Fisher, Larry-Fitzpatrick (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Flaks-Flynn (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Fogelman-Foster,Joyce (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Foster, Judith-Fox (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Frockelton-Freed (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Freedberg-Fried (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Friedman-Frost (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Fry-Furuichi (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Gabay-Gan (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Ganapathi-Garcia (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Gardell-Gaubatz (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Gardell-Gaubatz (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Georgi-Geyer (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Ghazarian-Gilboe (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Gilfillan-Giri (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Girotti-Glew (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Glick-Gold (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Goldberg-Goldstein (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Goldstone-Gorden (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Gordon-Gotto (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Gottschalk-Gray,Harry (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Gray, Horace-Greenblatt (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Greene-Griffin (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Griffith-Gross,Mary (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Gross, Myron-Grymes (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Gubits-Gupta (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Gurd-Guzelian (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Haas-Hahn (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Haidle-Haley (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Hall-Hamer (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Hamilton-Hampton (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Han-Hansford (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Hanson-Hardy (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Hare-Harrington (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Harris-Hartzell (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Harvey-Hattman (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Haugen-Hazuda (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Hearing-Heitz (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Held-Hempfling (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Henderson-Henrikson (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Henry-Herriott (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Hers-Heywood (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Hickman-Hilf (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Hill-Hinton (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Hirata-Hnilica (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Ho-Hoekstra (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Hof-Hoke (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Holbrook-Holloway (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Holmes-Holzbach (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Homandberg-Hopper (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Horne-Horwitz (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Hosein-Howland (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Hruby-Huang, Freesia (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Huang, Jung-Huang, WeiYong (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Hubbard-Hugli (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Hui-Hupe (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Hurlburt-Hyslop (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Ibsen-Imsande (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Inaba-Irving (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Isberg-Isom (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Member Files, Ito-Izawa (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Jack-Jacobson, Elaine (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Jacobson, Gary-Jamdar (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, James-Japa (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Jarabak-Jentoft (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Jerina-John (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Johnson, Alfred-Johnson, Jean (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Johnson, Jerry-Johnson, Nancy (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Johnson, Paul- Jonas (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Jones-Jorns (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Jörnvall-Julin (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Jump-Jurutka (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Kaback-Kaiser (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Kaiserman-Kane (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Kanfer-Kappel (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Karam-Karunatilake (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Kashket-Katunuma (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Katwa-Kawooya (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Kay-Keen (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Keenan-Kelly (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Kelmers-Kezdy (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Khachatrain-Khym (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Member Files, Kibler-Kim (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Kimball-Kingdon (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Kinkade-Kirtley (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Kishimoto-Klein (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Kleinman-Kluger (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Kmetec-Knutson (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Kobata-Kolesnick (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Kolodner-Koretz (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Koritz-Kotb (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Kow-Kramer (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Krane-Kress (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Krichevsky-Krutzsch (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Kubinski-Kumar, Kanesh (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Kumar, Raj-Kuo (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Kupfer-Kyte (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Labelle-Lal (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Lam-Lane (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Lang-LaPorte (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Largman-Lawrence (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Lawson-Leboy (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Leder-Lee, Kyung (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Lee, Lana-Lee, Yuan Chuan (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Leeb-Lundberg-Lei (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, LeMaster-Leung (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Lev-Levy (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Lewin-Li (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Lian-Lienhard (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Light-Lin (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Lincoln-Lippert (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Lippiello-Littauer (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Little-Lo (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Loach-Long (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Lingmore-Lovrien (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Low-Ludden (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Ludlum-Lusty (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Luthe-Lytton (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Ma-Mackman (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, MacLennan-Magun (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Mahadevappa-Maizels (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Majerus-Maltese (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Mancuso-Manos (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Mans-Marfey (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Margolies-Marians (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Markert-Marrs (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Marsh-Martensen (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Martin-Marzluff (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Mas-Mastro (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Matchett-Matsuno (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Matta-Matyas (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Mauk-Mazumder (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, McAllister-McClain (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, McClellan-McCune (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, McDaniel-McIntyre (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, McKay-McRorie (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Mead-Mehrabian (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Meinehofer-Melton (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Mendelsohn-Merola (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Merrick-Meyer (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Mhaskar-Mieyal (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Mikkelsen-Millar (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Miller-Miller,W. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Millet-Mistry (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Mitchell-Mizuno (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Mocharla-Molowa (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Momany-Mookerjea (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Moore-Moos (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Mora-Morlock (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Morre-Morton (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Mosbach-Mozersky (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Mroczkowski-Mukku (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Muldoon-Mulqueen (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Mumma-Murachi (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Murad-Murthy (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Mushahwar-Myers (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Na-Nakhasi (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Nakhla-Nazar (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Neal-Nelson (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Nemani-Newcombe (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Newgard-Nicholson (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Nick-Nilson (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Nimni-Nordblom (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Member Files, Nordin-Nyquist (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Obeid-O'Connor (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Odell-O'Connor (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Oka-Olsen (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Olson-Omura,Satoshi (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Omura, Tsuneo-Orkin (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Orlando-Ork (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Osaki-Oxols (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Pabo-Paladini (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Palayoor-Pang (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Panganamala-Park (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Parker-Patel, Ramesh (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Patel, Tarun-Payza (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Peabody-Pennell (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Penniall-Pervaiz (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Pesch-Pezzuto (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Pfeffer-Philo (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Piantadosi-Pirtle, Robert (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Pisano-Pluskal (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Pocker-Ponticorvo (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Pontremoli-Posner, Aaron (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Posner, Barry-Poyton (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Prahl-Price, Paul (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Price, Peter-Pryor (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Pueh-Putterman (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Qasba-Qureshi (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Raaka-Ramachandran (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Ramakrishna-Rao, Gadiparthi (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Rao, Gundu-Rawson (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Ray-Razzell (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Read-Redman (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Reeck-Reif (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Reilly-Rennert (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Renthal-Reznikoff (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Rhee-Rhodes (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Ribbons-Riley, Lela (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Riley, Monica-Rizack (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Ro-Robertson (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Member Files, Robertus-Roe (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Member Files, Roeder-Rongone (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Member Files, Ronwin-Rosenberg, Eugene (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Member Files, Rosenberg, Lawrence-Rosevear (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Member Files, Rosiers-Rothman, James (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Member Files, Rothman, Lucia-Royer (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Member Files, Rubenstein-Rushizky (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Member Files, Rushlow-Ryoji (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Member Files, Saari-Sadowski (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Member Files, Safa-Sajdera (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Member Files, Sakanari-Samy (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Member Files, Sanborn-Sanwal (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Member Files, Sapirstein-Sato (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Member Files, Sau-chi-Sazer (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Member Files, Scaduto-Schaup (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Member Files, Schechter-Scherberg (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Member Files, Schieber-Schloss (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Member Files, Schmaier-Schnoes (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Member Files, Scholten-Schroepfer (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Member Files, Schubart-Schutzbach (Box 51, Folder 20)